原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我想当妈妈
I want to be a mom.
我能拥有自己的家庭
I can have a family of my own.
我想向世人介绍梦想者
I wanna introduce the world to Dreamer.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我要抓住这个梦想者  立刻
I want this Dreamer detained. Now.
梦想者
Dreamer!
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我不知道你是怎么了
I don't know what happened to you,
但我会查清楚
but I'll find out.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我以为你在斯摩维尔
I thought you were in Smallville.
我忘了我的日记
I forgot my journal.
你看起来跟她一模一样
You really look exactly like her.
居然有人相信我袭击了白宫
People actually believe that I attacked the White House.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
我想让莱克斯下台  从而结束这一切
I want to take Lex down and put an end to all of this.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
-快走  -他什么都没做
- Let's go! - He didn't do anything!
你的孩子们刚失去了父亲
Your children, they just lost their father.
我可不想看到他们也失去母亲
I would hate to see them lose their mother, too.
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不  亲爱的
No! Sweetheart.
莱克斯买了导弹基地
Lex bought a missile base?
看来我们得去卡兹尼亚
Guess we're going to Kaznia.
我没有焦虑
I'm not anxious.
我只是觉得我一个人飞会更好  更快
I think it would just be better, faster, if I flew alone.
坐飞机飞
Commercial.
这架飞机是我自己设计的
I designed this jet myself.
没有比这个更快的了
There's no faster way to fly.
-是  -如果你想要保密
- Right. - And if you want stealth,
它还有军事级别的隐形技术
this has got military grade cloaking.
但是你没必要跟我一起去
Yeah, but you don't have to come with me.
我要在莱克斯被逮捕的时候看着他眼睛
I need to look Lex in the eye when we catch him.
我要让他知道是我干的
I need him to know it was me.
感觉像是回到参军的日子了
Feels like I'm back on deployment.
这么看来军事管制还是有些好处
Hey, at least that's one upside to martial law.
能让你感觉像是在家一样
Maybe you feel like you're at home.
你没事吧
You okay?
膝盖状态不好
Got a bum knee.
身体越来越差真是讨厌
It really sucks when your body starts breaking down.
是啊  真的
Yeah. Seriously.
有时候我会想怎么跑得没以前那么快了
Sometimes I wonder when I can't run as fast as I used to,
转念一想  "哦对  我已经不再是20岁了"
I'm like, "Oh, right, I'm not 20 anymore."
没人能幸免
No one is spared.
除了詹姆斯
James will be.
有个拥有超能力的手足肯定很奇怪吧
Must be strange to have a sibling with superpowers, huh?
-等一下  -好
- Oh, hey, hang on one sec. - Yeah.
我是艾丽克斯
This is Alex.
好
Yeah...
不好意思  什么
I'm sorry. What?
那...
That...
那么快吗  这...
That fast? It...
好吧  好的
Okay, yes. Um...
好的  谢谢  好  谢谢
Okay. Thank-- Yup. Thank you.
怎么了
What is it?
我得  我得回家了
I should... I should go home.
你没事吧  是谁打来的
Are you okay? Who was that?
是收养机构
That was the adoption agency.
我要当母亲了
I'm gonna be a mother.
我九岁的时候  我撞坏了门牙
When I was nine years old, I chipped my front tooth.
但那周末我要参演校园剧
But I was in my school play that weekend.
我去告诉我妈妈
I went to tell my mom that...
我没法去了
I couldn't do it,
然后她只是对我笑了笑
and she just smiled at me.
她把自己的门牙涂黑了
She had painted her front tooth black.
你总是在背后支持着我
You were always there for me
我知道你永远都会
and I know you always will be.
我爱你
I love you.
洛克伍德秘书
Secretary Lockwood?
我以为你今天不来了
I didn't think you were coming in today.
那个自称为梦想者的外星罪犯处理得怎样了
Where are we with the criminal alien who calls herself Dreamer?
-我不知道你...  -等一下
- I'm not sure what you-- - Wait a second.
这是超常活动调查部  对不对
This is the Department of Extra-Normal Operations, is it not?
我们在  我们在这个
What do we... what do we do here
超常活动调查部里做什么
at the Department of Extra-Normal Operations?
我们监控超常活动
We monitor Extra-Normal--
不不不  外星人  对吗  你是要...
No, no, no! Aliens. Right? That was your...
你是要说外星人  你说得对
You were gonna say alien. Well, you're correct.
梦想者是个外星人
And Dreamer is an alien.
如今我们不仅监控外星人  还要追捕他们
And these days, we don't just monitor aliens, we hunt them down.
那么  你逮捕梦想者了吗  没有吗
So, have you hunted down Dreamer yet? Huh? No?
好吧  问你个简单的问题
Okay. Here's an easy one.
杀死我妻子的那个外星人呢
What about the alien who killed my wife?
哈雷上校
Colonel Haley--
哈雷上校不在这里  我在
Colonel Haley isn't here. I am.
好了  听好
All right. Listen up.
一个非法外星人
An illegal alien
霸占了你们的广播信号
has commandeered your airwaves
召集人们对抗你们的政府
and called for an uprising against your government.
我们要找到她
We have to find her.
我们要查出她是谁
We have to find out who she is.
找到所有与她合作的人类与外星人
Find every human and alien whom she is working with.
我有个想法  让我们从詹姆斯·奥尔森开始
And, I have an idea, let's start with James Olsen
因为我想知道他是怎么
because I would like to know how the hell
获得超能力的
he got superpowers.
超 女
第四季 第二十集
孤独堡垒
不得不说  各位  我不太喜欢这样
Got to say, guys, I'm not a huge fan of this.
有意思
Intriguing.
我认为发现你能够燃烧
I should think discovering you're inflammable
会让你感到高兴
would be an emotional net-posiitve.
防火  你怎么一点也不兴奋
Flame-proof. How are you not more excited?
因为你才是让人兴奋的那个
Because you're the exciting one.
不那么温顺的新手记者
Not so mild-mannered cub reporter
变成受人敬仰的超级英雄
turned inspirational superhero?
我想说  我当时就知道你能行
I'm just happy to say I knew you when.
谢了  老大
Thanks, boss.
现在  我要用这个打你了
Now, I'm gonna hit you with this
看看会发生什么
and we're gonna see what happens.
我会叫你收敛点
And I'm gonna ask you to turn it down
因为我还没准备好
because I'm not ready for that yet.
本·洛克伍德去超查部了
Ben Lockwood is at the DEO.
可今天是他妻子的葬礼
But his wife's funeral is today.
我没料到这点
I did not account for this.
艾丽克斯刚刚给我发来信息
Alex just texted me moments ago
说她在处理私人事务
saying she was dealing with a personal matter
哈雷上校又去了特区
and Colonel Haley's in D.C.
试着撤销本·洛克伍德的许可
Trying to revoke Ben Lockwood's clearance.
我最好立即回去
It's best I return immediately.
你觉得你能应付他吗
You think you can handle him?
真正的问题是他能应付我吗
The real question is can he handle me?
小心点
Be careful.
好了
So...
-大锤时间  -不准打脸  孩子
- Hammer time? - Not in the face, kiddo.
不准打脸
Not in the face.
我知道
I know, right?
这架飞机能自己做咖啡
This plane makes its own coffee,
自己刷马桶  自己驾驶
cleans its own toilets and flies itself.
没有飞行员吗
There's no pilot?
人会犯错  我的科技不会
Well, humans make mistakes. My technology doesn't.
说到犯错
Speaking of mistakes,
我该从一开始就把莱克斯的事告诉你
I should have told you about Lex from the beginning.
我还在练习信任这种能力
Trust is still a learned skill for me.
我天生不具备这种特质
It doesn't come naturally.
无论如何
Well, no matter what,
我们永远在同一战线
we are always on the same side.
别担心  只是雷雨而已
Don't worry. It's just a lightning storm.
紫色的闪电常见吗
Is lightning usually purple?
系好安全带  我来让飞机着陆
Get your seat belt back on. I'm gonna land this plane.
卡拉  卡拉  准备好
Kara... Kara, brace yourself.
我们要紧急着陆
We're gonna make an emergency landing.
这我绝对不能接受
Yeah. That's gonna be a huge nope for me.
戴上氧气面罩  知道吗
Get your oxygen mask on, okay?
我要重启引擎
I'm gonna restart the engine.
逗我玩呢
Are you kidding?
好  我能行
Okay, I got this.
我能行
I got this.
我得重启电源
Okay... I gotta get the power back on.
-引擎已启动  -太好了
- Engine engaged. -Yes.
自动航行重启中  需要手动降落
Autopilot rebooting. Manual landing required.
不是吧
Seriously?
我的天  卡拉
Oh, my God. Kara.
卡拉
Kara.
卡拉  你还好吗
Kara, you okay?
我肯定是昏过去了
I must have passed out.
老天  我讨厌飞行
God! I hate flying.
那些闪电不是自然形成的
That lightning wasn't natural.
有人故意袭击我们
Someone brought us down on purpose.
但愿我们没有毁掉惊喜
Well, let's hope we didn't ruin the element of surprise.
卡兹尼亚
太奇怪了
This is so odd.
我还以为莱克斯背后会有一支军队
I would've thought Lex would have an army behind him.
肯定是几天前就撤离了
Must have left days ago.
闪电是怎么回事
What about the lightning?
自动化系统
Automated system.
-很有莱克斯的风格  -他们去哪了
- Very Lex. - Where did they go?
我的天
Oh, my God.
莱克斯做了些什么  做试验吗
What was Lex doing? Experimenting?
用外星人做试验
On aliens.
他试图吸出他们的能力加以利用
He was trying to siphon and harness their powers.
他折磨了他们
He was torturing them.
这上面都有艾美特克的标志
These all say AmerTek on them.
纸质文件
Paper files?
看起来好原始
Seems so low-tech.
她总说纸不会被骇客侵入
She always said you couldn't hack paper.
是伊芙  这是她的字迹
It's Eve. This is her handwriting.
开始读吧
Let's start reading.
那好
Okay, well,
这是孩子生母的档案
this is the birth mother's file.
里面有她的经历  她的病史
It's got her story, it's got her medical history.
我的天  她才17岁
Oh, my God. She's only 17.
好了  深呼吸
Okay, take a breath.
没有深呼吸的时间  她马上就生了
No, there's no time to breathe. She's already in labor.
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yeah.
她对所有人隐瞒了怀孕的事
She hid the pregnancy from everybody.
通常  生母会看潜在父母的档案
Usually, the birth mother looks at prospective parent profiles
然后选择三个
and then she chooses three.
但这次  因为她马上就要生宝宝了
But in this case, since she's about to have the baby,
她只选了一个
she's only chosen one.
就是我
And that's me.
艾丽克斯  这太棒了
Alex, that's incredible.
是太疯狂了
It's insane.
我只有12个小时来决定
I mean, I have 12 hours to decide
我想不想要一个孩子
if I want to have a child
然后赶去朴茨茅斯  孩子在那出生
and then get to Portsmouth where the baby is gonna be born.
我一年前填写了领养申请表
Look, I filled out the adoption application a year ago
从那以后一点消息都没有
and I haven't heard a single word since then.
犹如石沉大海
Not one word.
现在  突然间  我只有12小时
And now, all of a sudden, I have 12 hours
来做人生中最重大的决定
to make the biggest decision in my life.
你想做母亲吗
Do you wanna be a mother?
胜过一切
More than anything.
是的  当然想
Yes. Of course.
我因为这个和我未婚妻分手了
I... I mean, I left my fiancee over this. It...
她不想要孩子
She didn't wanna have kids.
那太艰难了
That's... that's so hard.
现在天下大乱  凯莉
I mean, the world is completely upside down, Kelly.
莱克斯·卢瑟还逍遥法外
Lex Luthor is still out there
该抓住他的人是我
and I'm the one who's supposed to catch him
然后还有戒严令
and then there's martial law.
我不能...
I mean, I can't--
我要怎么出门去买尿布呢
How would I even get out on the street and get diapers?
我会给你找尿布的
I will find you some diapers.
重点不是尿布
It's not about the diapers.
我知道不是  但你得喘口气
I know it's not. But you have to take a beat and breathe
一次解决一个问题
and look at the issues one at a time.
我真正需要的就是能和我妹妹聊聊
What I really need is to be able to talk to my sister
我联系不上她  她在卡兹尼亚
and she's unreachable. She's in Kaznia.
如果卡拉在的话
Okay. If Kara was here,
她会怎么说
what would she say?
好吧
Okay.
如果卡拉在的话  她会告诉我
If Kara was here, she would tell me...
这一直以来都是我的梦想
that this has always been my dream.
她会说
And she would say
永远都不会有合适的时机
that it's never gonna be the perfect time.
尽管
And that
坏人逍遥法外  还有戒严令
despite villains on the loose and martial law,
这是一份礼物
this is a gift
不欣然接受将会是一种亵渎
and it would be sacrilege not to accept it.
看来你有答案了
Sounds like you have your answer.
我找过哈雷的办公室了  找到了一些文件
I went through Haley's office. Found some files.
莉娜·卢瑟一直在超查部外工作
Lena Luthor's been working out of the DEO.
该死
Sprock.
为什么  整栋楼都是她的
Why? She's got a whole building with her name on it.
也许我们在她的实验室会找到答案
Maybe we'll find some answers in her lab.
带我去看看
Show me.
雪上加霜
Double sprock.
也许我能帮帮忙
May I be of some assistance?
把门打开
Open it.
我不能这么做
I can't.
这是命令
That's an order.
然而显然
Yet, it would appear that
根据超查局行为准则第六章第351条
Article 351 Section 6 of the DEO Code of Behavior
即使对总统的内阁也不能有例外
does not make exceptions for the President's cabinet.
库珀  枪给我
Cooper, sidearm.
等等  这是克匹人
Wait. This is Kopy.
去年秋天他袭击了狂欢节
He attacked that carnival last fall.
我还写了一篇关于他的报道
I wrote an article about him.
他可以自我克隆
Yeah, he could clone himself.
也不是
Not exactly.
他可以像细胞一样自我分裂
He could split himself like a cell.
每一个克隆都比本体更加强大
And, uh, each copy was more powerful than the original.
但是分裂得越久  就会变得越傻
But the longer they were separated, the dumber they got.
这些是超查局的超能力抑制手铐
Those are DEO power-dampening cuffs.
这里所有的实验对象
All of the test subjects here
都是超查部废弃楼的囚犯
were prisoners of the DEO Desert Facility.
这就是莱克斯监视这里的原因
That's why Lex was spying on it.
他在搞些什么
What is he building?
有人吗
Is someone there?
立刻出来  我们不会伤害你
Come out now and we won't hurt you.
伊芙
Eve?
卡拉  莉娜
Kara. Lena.
你们找到我了
You found me.
我好害怕
I was so scared.
莱克斯呢
Where's Lex?
我看到他对那些可怜外星人所做的事
I saw what he was doing to those poor aliens
我无法再支持他了
and I just couldn't stand by him anymore.
少废话了  伊娃·布劳恩
Cut the crap, Eva Braun.
你暗箭伤人  你就是个骗子
You're a backstabber and a liar.
你说得对  我是在骗你们
You're right. I am lying.
但我真的很喜欢你们
But I really do love you guys.
只是我更喜欢莱克斯
I just love Lex more.
我永远都会站在他那边
I'm always gonna be on his side.
你要去吃牢饭了
You're going to jail.
但无论是美国监狱
But whether it's an American prison
还是西伯利亚的地牢
or a Siberian hole in the ground,
都由我来决定
is up to me right now.
所以我们想知道什么  你都要从实招来
So, you're gonna tell us what we wanna know.
快说
Now.
朴茨茅斯
是的  我在酒店
Yes, I am. I'm at the hotel.
她感觉怎么样  她知道我来了吗
How is she feeling? Does she know that I'm here?
好吧  好好好  我...
Oh, okay, okay, good. Good, good, good. I...
懂了
I see. Yeah.
我明白  好的  谢谢你
Y-I... Yes, I-I understand. Okay. Th-Thank you.
-怎么样  -她的宫口刚刚开了四厘米
- Well? - She's only dilated to four centimeters
所以我们还要等一会
so we still have a while to wait, you know.
但是她的生命特征很稳定
But, um, I mean, she's... Her vitals are good,
没有危险的迹象
and there's no signs of distress,
一切都在正常进行
and everything is just progressing normally.
很好
Great.
那你为什么一副情况不好的样子
Why do you look like it's not great?
在孩子出生之前  她不想见我
She doesn't wanna see me until after she has the baby.
这个能理解
That's understandable.
当然  你说得对
Yeah, of course. Y-Yeah, you're right.
我当然说得对
Of course I'm right.
尽力放松一点
Now, try to relax.
吃点巧克力
Eat some chocolate.
如果我的公寓对宝宝来说不够安全怎么办
What if my apartment isn't safe for a baby?
你怎么知道家里有没有含铅油漆
You know, I mean, how do you know if you have lead-based paint?
只要做个简单测试就行
That is a simple test.
我每个角落都装了监视器
I've got wires everywhere.
我所有的电源插座都露在外面
And all of my... all of my outlets are exposed.
这个问题完全可以解决
That is totally fixable.
而且你的宝宝不会这么快学会爬的
And your baby's not gonna be crawling anytime soon.
是  但如果宝宝把自己抛到电源插座上怎么办
Right, but what if it, like, flings itself into an outlet?
你听到自己的话了吗
Do you hear yourself?
艾丽克丝
Alex,
你只是害怕了
you're just scared.
我不是害怕
I'm not scared.
是非常害怕
I'm terrified.
先从外星人开始说吧
Let's start with the aliens.
我们知道你们一直想利用他们的力量  为什么
We know you've been trying to harness their powers. Why?
我不...
I don't...
伊芙
Eve...
卡拉
Kara!
你本打算告诉我们外星人的事
You were about to tell us about the aliens.
莱克斯要对他们做什么
What does Lex do to them?
莱克斯喜欢对他的计划保密
Lex likes to keep his plans compartmentalized.
连他的一生挚爱也不告诉吗
Even from the love of his life?
你觉得我是他的一生挚爱吗
You think I'm the love of his life?
-我觉得你...  -他信任你是有原因的
- Oh, I think you're-- - He trusted you for a reason.
你帮助他在超查部罪犯身上做了实验
You were helping him experiment on DEO prisoners.
他怎么会接触得到他们
How did he get access to them?
有内部人员帮了他
Someone inside helped him.
你是说这次监狱转移有人授权吗
You're saying this was an authorized prison transfer?
-是的  -谁授权的
- Yes. - Who authorized it?
我不确定  政府的人  位高权重
I'm not sure. Someone in the government. Someone high up.
你到底一直在看什么
What do you keep looking at?
这些爪印通往某个地方
These claw marks lead somewhere.
-爸  -乔治
- Dad! - George.
乔治  你怎么来这里了
George! What are you doing here?
妈妈的葬礼你居然中途离场
You left in the middle of Mother's funeral.
我知道  但我别无选择
Yes, and I know. But I had to.
你也希望我抓到杀你母亲的凶手  对吗
You want me to catch your mother's killer, don't you?
我当然希望  但是
Of course I do, but you...
你把我丢在教堂里不管  而...
You left me alone in a church full of people and...
我刚失去我妈妈
I just lost my mother.
我需要你
And I need you.
我知道  但我们需要伸张正义  儿子
I know, but we need justice, son.
先是你爷爷  再是你妈妈
First your grandfather, now your mother.
我现在做的每件事都是为了纪念他们
Everything that I am doing is for their memories.
先生  我们发现了一样东西  你需要看看
Sir, we found something I think you're gonna wanna see.
我也是为了你
And for you.
我不希望失败
I just don't wanna fail.
你为什么觉得自己会失败
Why do you think you'd fail?
我妈妈
My mom was, uh...
她很会照顾我
She was incredible with me.
她总是在我哭的时候
I mean, she always just...
抱着我  陪伴我
hugged me when I cried, and she...
她会帮我处理伤处和淤青
fixed up my bumps and my bruises
还会跟我一起做科学项目
and work on my science projects with me.
她让我觉得我被爱意包围
And she made me feel so loved.
而且
And, you know,
在我成长期间  很艰难的时候
for a lot of my formative and toughest years,
她都是独自带我
she did it alone
也是她激励了我  让我觉得
and she is the one that inspired me to think
我可以独自完成这件事
that I can do this on my own.
但是现在...
But now that this is...
真的到了这一刻
I mean, it's right in front of me,
我忽然有点不确定
and I'm just not sure
我作为一名母亲  能否做得有她一半好
that I can even be half the mother that's she's been for me.
你听我说
Okay, look.
我认识你的时间不长
I've only known you for a short time.
但是根据我看到的
But from what I've seen,
你是我见过最会照顾别人的人
you're the most nurturing person that I've ever met.
你照顾你的朋友们
You take care of your friends,
你妹妹
your sister,
你还照顾了我住院的哥哥
you took care of my brother when he was in the hospital.
还有我  而我们甚至都不熟
And even me. Who you barely knew.
你如此在乎  不会失败的  艾丽克斯
You care too much to fail, Alex.
你绝对会成为一位称职的母亲
I mean, you are gonna be an amazing mother.
有没有人说过你应该去当心理医生
Did anyone ever tell you you should be a shrink?
有那么一两次
Once or twice.
-好了  把巧克力给我吧  -吃光了
- All right, give me the chocolate. - It's all gone.
-什么  -是啊
- What? - I know.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这是哈伦·艾尔
This is Harun-El.
氪石
Kryptonite.
这些都是用来伤害氪星人的设备
This is all equipment to hurt Kryptonians.
这是军事集结区  不可能
This is a staging area. Can't be.
看起来莱克斯在帮卡兹尼亚人入侵美国
Looks like Lex is helping the Kaznians to invade America.
计划是这样的
That's the plan.
但是卡兹尼亚人入侵美国
But a Kaznian invasion on American soil
就像一个孩子朝坦克扔石头
will be like a child throwing rocks at a tank.
莱克斯有坦克
Lex has a tank.
坦克
Tank.
-伊芙  -坦克  坦克  坦克
- Eve. - Tank. Tank. Tank.
-好了  -坦克
- All right. All right, - Tank.
坦克  坦克  坦克  坦克
Tank. Tank. Tank. Tank. Tank. Tank. Tank.
莱克斯肯定对她做了什么  设置了关键词
Lex must have done something to her. Trigger word.
那是超女
That's Supergirl.
莱克斯称之为Ryzhaya Dch
Lexie calls her Ryzhaya Dch.
是"红女儿"的意思
That's "Red Daughter."
很厉害
That's pretty badass.
是啊  快看这个运动婴儿车
Yeah. Wait, but check out the jogging strollers.
跑步都可以带着孩子  快看啊
You could take the baby on a run. Look at that.
这绝对是带孩子的正确做法
Okay, that is definitely the way to go.
我的天哪
Oh, my gosh.
天哪  她肯定是宫口全开了
Oh, my gosh. She must be fully dilated.
也就是说  孩子要出生了
that means... That means the baby's coming.
也就是说  我的天哪
That means... that-- Oh, my gosh.
喂  对  我是艾丽克斯  是的
Hello. Yes, this is Alex, yes.
什么
What?
不
No, I...
不  我知道你说过有这种可能
No, I know. I know that you said that that could happen,
但是你也说了  这种可能发生的几率
but you also said that there was a very minimal chance
在这种情况下非常低
of it happening in this case.
你确定吗
Are you certain?
是
Yeah.
我
I...
我明白你的意思  好
Yeah, I understand what you're saying. Yeah.
好
Okay...
好 谢谢
Okay. Thank...
怎么了
What happened?
孩子外公外婆
The grandparents called up, um,
请了一位牧师和孩子母亲谈话  她最后
a priest to talk to the mother and she ended up...
她改变了主意
She changed her mind
打算留下
and she's gonna keep...
打算留下孩子
She's gonna keep the baby.
她是克隆人吗
Is she a clone?
不  不算
No. Not exactly.
这些生物特征都受了哈伦·艾尔的影响
All these biometrics have been affected by Harun-El.
我们知道它能复制氪星人
We know it duplicates Kryptonians.
它分离了小萨和主宰
It split Sam from Reign.
超女肯定接触了它
Supergirl must have come in contact to it.
那这跟莱克斯有什么关系
But how does Lex fit into this?
卡兹尼亚人找他来帮忙控制她
Kaznians brought him in. He's helping them control her.
超女不可能跟莱克斯合作
Supergirl would never work with Lex.
她不是超女
It's not Supergirl.
她就是一块白板  至少以前是
She's a blank slate. Or at least she was.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
这是先天和后天的问题
It's a question of nature versus nurture.
她在全世界最专制的国家之一
She's been tested, trained, and indoctrinated by Lex
被莱克斯关在监狱里接受测试  训练  洗脑
in a prison in one of the most oppressive regimes in the world.
但她肯定有善良的一面
But she has to have good in her.
小萨也一样
There was good in Sam.
但主宰是个恶魔
And Reign was a monster.
莱克斯创造了他最害怕的东西
Lex has created the very thing he fears the most.
训练有素的氪星杀人武器
Kryptonian weapon trained as a killer.
这武器在莱克斯手里
And in Lex's hands,
比原子弹更危险
it's more dangerous than an atomic bomb.
而他现在用它来对付美国
And he has it pointed right at America.
是她  不是它
She is not an it.
或许莱克斯塑造了她
Lex may have molded her
但她肯定保留了超女的某些品质
but there has to be some part of Supergirl still in her.
血红之女  她还在吗
Red Daughter... Is she still here?
伊芙  她去哪了
Eve. Where is she?
显然跟莱克斯在一块
With Lex, obviously.
伊芙
Eve.
但哈伦·艾尔不能复制人类
But the Harun-El can't duplicate humans.
他用了克匹人
He used Kopy.
你们两个不该在这
The two of you shouldn't be here.
既然来了  那就待一会吧
But as long as you are, stay a while.
十分钟后启动自毁
楼就要倒了  我们还有十分钟时间逃离
We've got ten minutes before this building comes crashing down.
快
Come on.
就是这个
This is it.
詹姆斯·奥尔森的能量就是这里来的
This is what gave James Olsen powers.
先生
Sir...
参与这项目的人都有一个共同的想法
Everyone involved in this project thought the same thing.
如果人类有超能力就好了
Wouldn't it be great if humans had superpowers?
他们在急救詹姆斯·奥尔森的时候
James Olsen was given a carefully calibrated highly refined dose
并注入了高纯度的精确剂量
in the midst of a medical emergency.
停停停  你等一下
Wait, wait, wait. Hold up. Hold up.
让他说完
Let him finish.
你手上拿的是未经加工和稀释的试验血清
What you're holding is a raw, undiluted experimental serum
它很可能会要了你的命
that will, in all likelihood, kill you.
"很可能会"  就是说有可能不会
"In all likelihood." That means it might not.
这个可能性我知道
I know the odds.
并不高
They're not good.
你很难过
You're grieving.
你想找到那个应该对此负责的人
You wanna find the person responsible.
你的儿子现在需要你
Your son needs you now.
先生  我们找到了杀死你妻子的外星人
Sir, we found the alien that killed your wife.
在哪
Where?
目标已定位
立刻派特工过去
Get our agents over there right now.
他们都在外搜查
They're all out searching.
那就组建一个超查部突击小队
Then assemble a DEO strike team.
我领头
I'll lead.
快去
Go!
八分钟后启动自毁
-我走右边  -我走左边
- I'll go right. - I'll go left.
天啊
Oh, my God.
该死
Damn it.
卡拉
Kara?
不要  不要
No. No.
这边没有出路  你那边...
Hey, there's no way out back this way. Is there--
不对  不对
No, no, um...
还有  还有点...
There's... there's just...
别紧张  没什么好害怕的
Hey, it's okay. There's nothing to be afraid of, right?
我们经历过更危险的情况  对不对
We've been through worse scrapes than this together, okay?
-对  那...  -等等  莉娜
- Right. So-- - Wait, wait, Lena...
还有...
There...
我们可以往上走
We can go up.
通风口  对
The air vent. Yeah.
七分钟后启动自毁
卡拉  你来吧
Kara, your turn.
我...
I, uh...
我忘记拿磁带录音机了
I forgot my tape recorder.
卡拉
Kara?
卡拉  快点
Kara, come on!
停下  不许动
Freeze! Don't move!
杀我妻子的那个布瓦克在哪
Where's the Brevakk who killed my wife?
-是她  -抓到了
- That's her! - I got her.
带她走
Take her out of here.
把这些人带去准备强化审讯
And rendition the lot of them for enhanced interrogation.
秘书先生
Mr. Secretary,
我们要找的人已经找到了
we found who we were looking for.
剩下的外星人是无辜的
The rest of these aliens are innocent of any crimes.
他们窝藏杀人凶手
They were harboring a murderer.
按我说的做
Move.
四分钟后启动自毁
感谢上帝  伊芙有恋纸癖
Well, thank God for Eve's paper fetish.
谢谢
Thanks.
超查部犯人转移
The DEO prisoner transfers.
莎拉·沃克
莎拉·沃克签字授权了
Signed and authorized by Sarah Walker.
总统的参谋长吗
The President's Chief of Staff?
她是政府里的间谍
She is the mole in the government.
和莱克斯一起工作
She's working with Lex.
是伊芙  我去找她  你去找证据
It's Eve. I'll get her, you get the evidence.
不  莉娜  等等
No, Lena, wait.
洛克伍德秘书
Secretary Lockwood.
英雄和纯血统叛徒
The hero and the blood traitor.
我正希望你们能过来
I was hoping you would come by.
逮捕他们
Arrest them.
厉害  你找到了我的飞机
Oh, good. You found my plane.
我本不想走到这一步
I hoped it wouldn't come to this.
真的吗
Really?
可是我想
'Cause I did.
这是个惊喜
This is a surprise.
逮捕他们
Arrest them!
不  我们每个人都宣誓
No! Each one of us swore an oath
要捍卫这个国家及其宪法
to defend this country and its constitution.
秘书在要求你们违背这个誓言
The Secretary is asking you to compromise that oath.
我劝你们  跟着心走
I urge you. Follow your hearts.
而不是命令
Not your orders.
谢谢你  下一个
Thank you. Next.
一分钟后启动自毁
该我了
My turn.
莱克斯只是在利用你
Lex was only using you, you know.
莱克斯爱我
Lex loves me.
莱克斯爱的只有他自己
The only person Lex loves is himself.
大家快趴下
Everybody, get down.
五
四
三
二
一
卡拉
Kara!
地球第一
Earth first.
下台和受苦选一个
Stand down or suffer.
我真希望你没逼我这么做
I wish you didn't make me do that.
谢谢你  卡拉
Thank you, Kara.
飞机上的蛇
Snake on a plane.
你以为自己肩负着全世界痛苦的重担
You think you have the weight of the world's pain on your shoulders.
但你没有
But you don't.
你制造了这种痛苦和恐惧
You created this pain, this fear.
你完全不了解我  外星人
You know nothing about me, alien.
我是火星猎人
I am the Martian Manhunter.
我认识你  你该知道...
I know you and you should know this...
上一个反对我的人
The last man who stood against me
把自己搞垮台了
met a downfall all of his own making.
不会再垮台了  我就是法律
There will be no downfall. I am the law.
只是现在
For now.
但政权变了
But regimes change.
油罐车
The tanker.
相信我
Trust me.
把这些外星人带到安全的地方
Let's get these aliens somewhere safe.
卡拉
Kara!
Kara.
我没事  一切都好
I'm okay. Everything's fine.
天啊
Oh, God.
感谢上帝你还好
Thank God you're all right.
-你找到泰斯马克了吗  -是的
- Did you find Tessmacher? - Yeah.
这不是真的泰斯马克
It wasn't the real Tessmacher.
或许一直都不是
Maybe it never was.
但是没关系
But it's okay.
现在我们知道莱克斯的目的
Now we know what Lex has been up to
以及他的帮手了
and who was helping him.
我们现在都知道了
Now we know everything.
很抱歉我把你一个人留在身后
I'm so sorry I left you alone back there.
让你置身于危险
Put you in danger.
我没事  我没事
I was fine. I am fine.
我一看到伊芙就发火了
When I saw Eve, I just saw red.
一下就想起最初的背叛
Shot me right back to the initial betrayal.
我当时思维不清晰
I... wasn't thinking clearly.
你不用向我做任何解释
You don't have to explain anything to me.
我知道她把你伤得有多深
I know how much she hurt you.
卡拉  拜托  我想向你道歉
Kara! Please! I'm trying to apologize to you.
那场爆炸可能杀了你
That explosion could have killed you.
不会的
It... it wouldn't have.
-莉娜  -我从不放松警惕
- Lena - I don't let my guard down ever.
可我轻信了伊芙  她背叛了我
And I did with Eve and she betrayed me.
我招她进来  可她对我撒谎
I let her in and she lied to me.
每一天  当着我的面
Every day. To my face.
在她的身份上撒谎
About who she was.
这就是最伤的地方
And that's what hurts.
我不知道自己能不能走出来  但是...
I don't... I don't know if I'll ever recover from it, but...
我知道  要不是
I know there is no way
你的友谊和正直
I could ever trust anyone ever again
我就再也
if it wasn't
不能信任任何人了
for your friendship and your integrity.
那对我意味着世界  卡拉
It just... It means the world to me, Kara.
我会一直在你身边的
I'm always gonna be here for you.
离开未婚妻的时候  我...
When I left my fiancee, I, uh...
这事都很难说出口
It's hard to even say that.
我觉得我永远都不会恢复
I felt like I would never heal.
但我还是做到了
But then I did.
后来  这...
And then, this...
整个经历
whole experience just
感觉就像是伤口又被撕开了
feels like that wound just got ripped right back open again.
这一次  我不...
And this time, I don't...
我不知道还能不能挺过去
I don't know if I can survive that.
-伤口愈合  -成了疤痕
- Wounds heal. - Into scars.
随着时间而消失
That fade in time.
有些人留下了不可磨灭的印记
Some people leave indelible marks
就像一块荣誉勋章  戴在身上
and you get to wear them like a badge of honor
体现出你从中学到的东西
of what you learn from the experience.
是吗  你从你的伤疤中学到了什么
Yeah? What did your scars teach you?
万事总有第二次机会
That there are always second chances.
如果你够有勇气迈出这一步的话
If you're brave enough to take the leap.
说起来容易做起来难
It's easier said than done.
我曾经订过婚
I was engaged.
詹姆斯从未说过
James never mentioned that.
因为他根本不知道
Yeah, well, he didn't know.
没人知道
No one did.
因为我爱上了我的军士
Because I was in love with my sergeant.
我们不能在国外服役时出柜
And we couldn't be out while serving abroad.
发生了什么
What happened?
她在巡逻时死了
She died while on patrol.
我都无法哀悼她
And I couldn't mourn her.
我就呆住了
I was just numb.
独自一人深陷在痛苦之中
Alone in my pain.
我
And, I, um...
在我回国后几个月  才能面对这件事
I didn't face it until I was back Stateside a few months later.
我以为这个伤永远不会愈合
I thought that wound would never heal.
然后我收到了她的告别信
And then I got her farewell note.
服役人员有时在任期前会寄出这些信
Service members send them sometimes before tours of duty
以防她们回不来了
in case they don't come back home.
我从来没想过会读到她的告别信
I never thought that I'd have to read hers.
她说她坚信
She said that she had every faith
我会找到另一个能让我笑的人
that I would find another person who would make me smile.
你也一样
And so will you.
在任何事上  你都会有第二次机会
You will get a second chance at everything.
别失去希望
Don't lose hope.
今天
Today,
必定是一个很深的伤口
this is absolutely a deep wound.
但总有一天
But someday,
这个伤疤将会脱落
it'll be a faded scar.
-儿子  -别这样
- Son... - Don't.
我来找你  你却拒绝了我
I came to you and you turned away from me.
你必须明白  孩子  我必须找到
You have to understand, son. I had to find--
杀害妈妈的凶手  对吗
Mom's killer. Right?
有用吗
Did it help?
你要知道  我今天看见你了
You know, I saw you today.
就是个痛苦愤怒的男人
Just another bitter, angry man.
乔治  乔治
George? George.
我所做的一切都是为了保护你和你母亲
I did this all to keep you and your mother safe.
你是为了你自己
You did this for yourself.
她死了都怪你
You're responsible for her death.
你用你那愚蠢的斗争杀了她
You killed her with this stupid fight of yours
我永远不会原谅你
and I will never forgive you.
我恨你
I hate you.
-血红之女吗  -对
- Red Daughter? - Yup.
我知道我应该怕她
I know I should be afraid of her,
但我有点替她难过
but I kind of feel bad for her.
如果我降落在其他地方  那可能就是我
I mean, if I had landed anywhere else, that could have been me.
一个被当做武器养大的难民
A refugee raised as a weapon.
但如果莉娜在那一刻发现了你的真实身份
But if Lena had found out in that moment who you really are...
我差点就告诉她了
I almost told her myself.
莱克斯已经知道了
Lex already knows.
你为什么又不告诉莉娜了呢
What stopped you from telling Lena?
过去几个月  莱克斯  伊芙都背叛了她
The past few months, she's been betrayed by Lex, by Eve...
如果她发现我一直都在骗她
So, if she found out after all this time I was lying...
我不能让她再经历那样的事了
I couldn't bear to put her through that again.
但是  等这一切都结束  莱克斯进了监狱
But, when this is all over, and Lex is behind bars,
我会亲口告诉她真相
I am going to tell her the truth.
就算她会恨我
Even if she hates me.
我必须这样做  因为这样才正确
I have to. It's the right thing to do.
是的  你说得对
It is. I think you're right.
你要怎么处理你在地图上找到的东西
And what are you gonna do about what you found on that map?
我作为一个美国公民的职责
My duty as an American citizen.
总统先生
Mr. President.
谢谢你肯与我见面
Thank you for seeing me.
欢迎  欢迎
Welcome. Welcome.
我对凯特·格兰特的媒体帝国深怀敬意
I have nothing but respect for Cat Grant's media empire.
对她的怒火深怀敬畏之心
And nothing but fear of her wrath.
那是氪石吗
Is that Kryptonite?
眼神犀利啊  女士
Ah. Sharp eye, young lady.
自从超女袭击了白宫
Ever since Supergirl attacked the White House
我们添加了一些必要的预防措施
we've added some necessary precautions to, uh,
来保护我
keep me safe.
我们是要谈什么
So, where do we start?
美国处于危险之中  先生
The United States is in danger, sir.
我是来提醒你的
I came here to warn you.
提醒我
Warn me?
提醒我什么
Of what?
莱克斯·卢瑟联合了卡兹尼亚政府
Lex Luthor has allied with the Kaznian government
他们准备发起攻击
and they are going to attack.
而且也不是超女攻击了你
And Supergirl didn't attack you.
是莱克斯手下的一个克隆人干的
A clone that worked for Lex did.
而你的幕僚长也与他勾结
And your Chief of Staff is in collusion with him.
你有  你有证据吗
Do you... do you have any proof?
谢谢你提醒我注意这件事
Well, I wanna thank you for bringing this to my attention.
丹弗斯小姐  有其他人看过这个证据吗
Now, Miss Danvers, has anyone else seen this evidence?
没有  我认为来提醒你更重要
No, I, I thought it was more important to warn you,
越快越好
as soon as possible.
你做的没错
You did the right thing.